One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was a crybaby
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
The word "thank you" has faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
I don't know the answer yet
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to lose something precious
The voice inside of me
keeps sustaining me
Wicked rain will get in my way
But I won't walk away
So let's go
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to lose something precious
To the future I believe in...
There's a tunnel of fire in the smoke!
You've always been like this!
Luffy!
You've never listened to me...
and you've always done crazy things like this!
Ace!!
F-Fire Fist Ace is...
now free!
Great! You did it, Straw Hat!
He rescued Ace!
He has been relentless since
Impel Down! That guy is really...
Something else!
Don't lose your cool! Be ready to fire!
Shoot them when they land!
Yes, sir!
Stay alert, Luffy! Let's split up for now!
Okay!
Oh no!
Flame Commandment!
Fire Pillar!
He's strong! Be careful!
Can you fight, Luffy?
Of course!
Ace-san! Luffy-kun!
Remember! Fire Fist
Ace is fire- he's a Logia!
I never thought that you'd be the one saving me.
Thanks, Luffy!
Old guy Whitebeard and the others helped me out!
Don't think that you're safe now!
Your execution will take place here now!
Now's our chance!
I'll cut you to pieces!
He's my brother! Leave him alone!
Fire Fist!
They make a good team.
Clear the way so they can get away!
Don't let them get away at any cost!
Firefly!
Fiery Doll!
Execute Fire Fist and Straw Hat!
Rubber-Rubber...
Jet Gatling!
You've gotten stronger, Luffy!
I'll be stronger than you someday!
In that case, I'll protect you for now.
That bastard!
Ice Block!
Stand aside, Luffy.
Pheasant Beak!
Mirror Flame!
Fleet Admiral-dono!
I can't believe this blunder!
Even I couldn't stop it!
Let them go! That way, things
will be more interesting!
Cut the crap!
Even an admiral's power
is useless against them!
How can we fight them?!
Don't lose your head!
Admiral Sakazuki!
We won't let them get away from here!
Mr. 2...
I hardly granted your wish.
And now, I need to hurry and escape...
To whom does this traitor owe allegiance?!
No, he's a prisoner impersonating a guard!
Oh no!
Heads up, everyone! Their ship is moving!
Don't get close! It's running
on the ground with its paddles!
Hey, who's controlling it?
Squard!
The Whirl Spider Pirates!
Pops, everyone, run!
Leave the war to us!
Those fools!
Don't be stupid, Squard!
Obviously, you have a death wish!
Of course I do.
What I did to Pops was horrible.
Even if this doesn't make amends for it,
I can't let things go like this!
I'm sorry, guys. I shouldn't have let you come with me.
It's okay, Captain! Don't worry!
We followed you because we wanted to!
We'll choose where to die on our own!
Captain! We'll follow you to the end!
I'm sorry...
Everybody, take Ace and run!
St. Elmo's Fire!
Fool!
Damn Squard! That's not
the smart way to do it!
Hey! Hurry up and get these cuffs off me!
What happened?!
The ship stopped moving!
Pops!
Can't you understand how
ungrateful it is for a child...
to die before his parent, Squard?!
Don't get too confident!
The stab wound you gave me isn't going to kill me!
Everybody grows old and dies eventually!
We accomplished our goal here!
There's no need for us to keep fighting here!
Pops!
Listen carefully, Whitebeard Pirates!
I'm going to give you all my final order as your captain!
"Final order"?!
Wait a second, Pops! That sounds sad!
I don't want to hear that!
Let's go back to the New World together!
Cross Fire!
Pops!
It is time for us to part ways!
Everyone, survive at any cost and
return to the New World safely!
P-Pops! Are you planning to die here?!
I'm a relic of a bygone era!
There is no ship that can carry me into the new age!
Escape from here, everyone!
Whitebeard!
No, Pops!
He gave us an order! We need to go!
Old guy!
Pops!
This is unbelievable!
Hey, why do you look so out of spirits?
Join us! There's more than enough treasure!
Never mind that guy.
He's not interested in treasures.
That's odd! What kind of pirate is he?
What is it that you want?
Hey, Newgate!
I've been traveling a very long time.
Let's get it over with!
Navy!
Marineford is in danger!
Stop Whitebeard!
Absolute Justice
He's willing to destroy the whole island!
Pops!
I don't wanna leave you!
You gotta come with us!
Pops!
Are you going to disobey your captain's orders?!
Escape from here, you brats!
Now is our chance! Kill
Whitebeard! He's dying already!
Pops!
Hurry up! Let's do as Pops said!
You don't mind leaving Pops behind?!
Yeah!
Stupid! No one wants to leave him behind!
Then...
Grumbling about it at a time like this...
is the same as trampling on Pops' determination!
Don't you understand?!
Pops!
Hurry and get ready to sail out!
Ace!
We're gonna leave soon! Hurry up and board the ship!
Commander Marco, let's go!
Pops...
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
Since he isn't concerned about
Fire Fist Ace anymore...
It's clear that his intention is to
sink Marineford into the ocean.
Along with himself!
Vice Admiral Garp! You're all right!
He wants to bring this era to a close?
I guess the time is right.
What happened to Whitebeard?!
Are the allies he sold out all dead now?!
What is happening at Marineford right now?!
What?!
The Transponder Snail isn't coming out?!
Damn! Captain Buggy is about to defeat
Whitebeard! There's no time for this!
Don't say it like it's an easy thing to do!
He may be dying, but he's still super strong! Have they been paying attention?!
Why did I tell them I was going to defeat that man?!
I really messed up!
I can't do it! It's impossible!
What?! We gotta broadcast Captain
Buggy's big moment all over the world!
Get it out at any cost!
Come out now!
Or we're gonna burn you out of it!
The Transponder Snail came out on its own!
Alright, capture my bravery!
Hey, look!
The video is back!
Um, well...
Transponder Snail, go lower!
Hi, everyone! I'm Buggy and I'm a legend!
You again?!
Get to the sea now!
We survivors need to return to the New World safely!
Don't let them get away!
Kill as many as you can!
I'm the only one that you
ought to worry about!
Commander Jozu!
He's badly injured, but he should be fine!
Our Captain gave us an order! Come with us!
Blenheim! You gotta carry Jozu!
Straw Hat-boy! Why are you standing around?!
Ace, let's go! The old man
has made up his mind...
I know! And it won't be in vain!
Back off, you bastards!
We don't need words now.
Just tell me one thing, Ace.
Were you happy to have me as your father?
You still tryin' to stand up?
I'd hate to see you die here, kid.
If you still want to fight, then take my name and roam the seas wild and free!
Become my son!
Of course I am!
Run! Run to the ship!
Ace-san, Luffy-kun, get in front of me!
Jinbe!
They want to get you two!
But Pops wants there to be as many survivors as possible!
Pops!
We've stolen a Navy ship! Get on board quickly!
Do they really think that they can
get away?! What a simple bunch.
Admiral Sakazuki!
You guys, move aside a little bit!
You two, just keep going
until you reach the ship!
As soon as you rescue
Fire Fist Ace, you run!
The Whitebeard Pirates must be a group of cowards!
What?!
He's obviously trying to stir us up!
If you stop, you'll just be playing into his hands!
Well, considering who your captain is, it's no surprise to me.
Because after all, Whitebeard is just a...
loser from a bygone era!
Ace!
A loser?
Take back what you just said!
Hey, don't, Ace! Don't stop!
He can say whatever he wants!
He's mocking Pops.
Ace!
Did you ask me to take it back?
That'll never happen! And here's why.
Your real father, Gold Roger, conquered the Grand Line...
and opened the door to the Great Pirate Era.
As a Navy admiral, I shouldn't be the one to say this...
but he was true to his name:
the King of the Pirates!
In comparison, what has Whitebeard done?
I wonder if he really had
the intention to fight...
I assume that he established
a large family somewhere...
and was satisfied with being a big fish in a little barrel.
There are some fools in this world...
who say that he was able to keep the peace on various islands...
but in my opinion, all he did was make weak pirates live in fear of him...
and he thinks that it made him a hero! What a joke!
When Roger was around, Whitebeard was always second in billing...
and even after he died, Whitebeard could never become the King.
He was never able to surpass Roger...
and that makes him a loser in life!
That is the truth about Whitebeard.
When you think about it, his existence was sad. He gathered a bunch of punks who called him Pops...
and roamed the seas
with his fake family.
Stop it.
And although he reigned the sea for decades...
he couldn't become the King, and gained nothing
and at the end, he was stabbed by a fool, one of his sons who fell for my trick...
and now he will die to protect that son.
Don't you think that he lived a worthless life?
Stop it!
Don't do it, Ace, come back!
Pops gave us a home!
You'll never understand his greatness!
People don't deserve to live
if they can't live justly!
Punks like you guys don't
deserve a place to live!
Stop it!
Whitebeard will die as a loser! It's
fitting for a big fish in a little barrel!
Whitebeard is a great pirate
who shaped this era!
Don't make fun of the man who saved me!
Don't do it, Ace!
The name of this era is "Whitebeard!"
Both Whitebeard and those who called him Pops...
are just losers!
Ace was burned!
Are you being careless because you ate...
a Logia type Devil Fruit, the most powerful type?!
You're just fire. My magma can burn even you!
My powers are far superior to yours!
Ace!
Hey, Luffy-kun, you shouldn't fight anymore!
Ace's Vivre Card!
Gold Roger the Pirate King and Dragon the Revolutionary!
I was surprised to hear that the sons of those two were blood-brothers.
You're both criminals by blood!
I don't care if the others get
away as long as I get you two!
Watch what I do.
Wait!
Luffy!